WASEEM KASHIF

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Ansar Gallery Barwa, Doha, Qatar | waseemqulandar@gmail.com | 30078398 | https://profile-portfolio-nine.vercel.app/



PROFILE

Passionate Full Stack Web Developer with a knack for creating intuitive and high-performing web applications. I excel at motivating, mentoring & developing teams of less experienced developers. I have 6 years of experience and ambitious web design professional seeking an opportunity as a web developer. Detail-oriented professional with an associate degree in computer science and proven experience with a web development firm and E-commerce Group.

Please visit my website to see projects I have done: https://profile-portfolio-nine.vercel.app/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer, Ansar Gallery, ansargallery.com, Doha, Qatar

March 2024 — Present

- · Lead development of features for ansargallery.com, enhancing user experience and functionality of ansargallery.com
- Implement responsive design using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks, ensuring compatibility across devices.

Web Developer, Uconnect Technologies, Gilgit, Pakistan

December 2021 — February 2024

- Worked with international clients as a freelancer developed, https://globalcqed.com/, https://www.letsgo.letshego.com/, GilgitApp.com and others.
- · Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality web applications on time.
- Implemented REST APIs to enhance application functionality and user experience.
- Mentored junior developers, fostering skill development and knowledge sharing.
- Utilized Git for version control, ensuring efficient project management and collaboration.

Junior Frontend Developer, Uconnect Technologies, Gilgit, Pakistan January 2021 — December 2021

Worked on various web development projects as junior developer along with a senior developer as a freelancer. Responsible for converting figma designs into real time responsive web applications using required technologies.

Technical Support Engineer, StromFiber, Karachi

August 2020 — December 2020

• For 6 months I worked as an IT Support Engineer for StromFiber Internet Services, a leading company providing GIPON internet to major cities in Pakistan.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML	CSS	JavaScript	Rest API's
Next.js	TypeScript	GIT	Prisma
React.js	Vue.js	SvelteKit	Redux
Tailwind CSS	Material UI	Magento	Next-Auth
Node Js	Express Js	PostgreSQL	

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science

May 2016 — July 2020

Igra University, Karachi, Pakistan

HSSC II July 2013 — July 2015

Aga Khan Higher Secondary School, Karachi

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Links: GitHub, Portfolio,LinkedIn
- · Languages: Urdu, English, Shina, Burushki